There was an earthquake in Highfield in 2021 and Timmy survived.
Sandy is reading his story.
The Highfield Earthquake It was about two o'clock in the afternoon.
I was working when the earthquake started.
At first I felt a slight shake, then I heard a loud noise like thunder.
Soon the real noise came like bombs under the ground.
The earth started to shake.
People shouted in fear.
Some ran out of the building.
I tried my best to run out too.
Outside people were running in all directions while pieces of glass and bricks were raining down.
Then the walls began to come down too.
Finally the noise and shaking ended.
It was dark and silent around me.
I couldn't see anything at all.
I didn't know if anyone else was around me.
I felt nervous and my heart was beating really fast.
I'm trapped, I said to myself.
A moment of fear went through my mind, but I told myself to calm down since I was still alive.
I shouted for help.
I thought somebody could hear me, but no one came for a very long time.
I knew I had to save energy and wait for help.
Hours later, as I was trying to find my way out, I suddenly heard some noise above me. Help! Please help! I'm here!
I cried out in a weak voice.
Then I heard shouts from excited people.
They quickly moved away the bricks.
At last, I was safe.